<idea-plugin>
    <id>com.applause.a11y.fixer.plugin.applause-a11y-fixer-plugin</id>

    <name>Applause Accessibility Tool</name>
    <description>
        <![CDATA[
        <p>
            The Applause Accessibility Tool from Applause Labs enables you to quickly identify and resolve accessibility issues
            while you code to help maintain a baseline of accessibility.
        </p>
        <br>

        <p>
            The tool flags violations to accessibility web standards and best practices that can accurately be detected via
            automation. For each issue identified, the tool provides either a code change that can be automatically applied or
            highlights the issue so that it can be corrected manually.
        </p>
        <br>

        <p>
            The Applause Accessibility Tool identifies many defects but should be used alongside manual testing to uncover the
            portion of accessibility issues that require human evaluation to detect.
        </p>
        <br>

        <strong>Key Features:</strong>
        <ul>
            <li>Integrates seamlessly into the web development process</li>
            <li>Fast and easy to use with no advanced accessibility knowledge required</li>
            <li>Flags accessibility issues early in the development process</li>
            <li>For non-subjective issues, provides a code updates to resolve the defect that can be automatically applied</li>
            <li>For subjective issues, provides a clear recommendation to resolve the defect that requires the user’s input to
                resolve
            </li>
            <li>Helps make web content more accessible to all users</li>
        </ul>
        <br>

        <p>Use of this plugin is subject to the Applause Terms and Conditions.</p>
        ]]>
    </description>
    <vendor>Applause</vendor>

    <idea-version since-build="192.*" until-build="193.*"/>

    <depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>
    <depends>com.intellij.modules.lang</depends>
    <depends>com.intellij.modules.xml</depends>

    <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij"/>

    <actions>
        <group id="com.applause.a11y.A11yActionGroup"
               class="a11y.actions.A11yActionGroup">
            <add-to-group group-id="EditorPopupMenu"/>
            <add-to-group group-id="ProjectViewPopupMenu"/>
            <add-to-group group-id="EditorTabPopupMenu"/>
            <add-to-group group-id="ConsoleEditorPopupMenu"/>
            <action id="com.applause.a11y.FixAction" class="a11y.actions.A11yFixAction"/>
            <action id="com.applause.a11y.ReportAction" class="a11y.actions.A11yReportAction"/>
        </group>
    </actions>

    <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
        <applicationService serviceImplementation="a11y.service.A11yService"/>
        <editorNotificationProvider
                implementation="a11y.notification.A11yNotificationProvider"/>
        <preloadingActivity
                implementation="a11y.init.PreloadA11yExecutable"/>
    </extensions>

</idea-plugin>
